(Amy:)It really can.
(Penny:)All right.
(Sheldon:)Nothing about
this is fun.
(Penny:)No one wants to
talk about flags,
(Sheldon:)and I haven't spoken
in over ten minutes,
(Sheldon:)so, enjoy your
new show, Internet.
Dr. Amy Farrah Flower
Present... With.
KOOTHRAPPALI:
I'm sorry for bothering you.
(Raj:)I'll hang up now.
(Amy:)No, hold on, Rajesh.
(Amy:)You know, you're not being
very sympathetic.
You know firsthand
that breakups are hard.
(Bernadette:)Fine.
(Sheldon:)If you insist on making
me a part of this,
(Sheldon:)yes, I knowledge how
painful they can be.
(Sheldon:)However, pain has an
evolutionary purpose.
(Sheldon:)It provides information
from the environment
that, uh, behavior
isn't good for us.
KRIPKE: Like when I fell in love
with that stripper
and bought her a Prius.
(Amy:)I'm just gonna push
all the buttons.